Wow!
&rlm;يا إلهي!
Look at all the yachts!
&rlm;انظر إلى كل هذه اليخوت!
How far can ships like those go?
&rlm;ما أقصى مسافة &rlm;قد تبحرها هذه السفن؟
To a whole other country! All the oceans are connected!
&rlm;إلى بلد آخر! &rlm;كل المحيطات متصلة!
I wish I could go aboard one.
&rlm;أتمنى لو يمكنني الصعود على متن إحداها.
I know what you mean.
&rlm;وأنا أيضاً.
That's nice and all,
&rlm;كل هذا لطيف
but I'm hungry, so let's head back and eat our bento lunches.
&rlm;لكنني جائع، لذا لنعد أدراجنا &rlm;ونأكل غداءنا المعد مسبقاً لنا.
Genta, you're all appetite for food and no appetite for adventure.
&rlm;"جنتا"، لديك شهية كبيرة للطعام &rlm;وليست لديك أي شهية للمغامرة.
Whoa, that looks awesome!
&rlm;هذا يبدو رائعاً!
Um, where are you going?
&rlm;إلى أين أنت ذاهب!
This must be it... Mr. Takiguchi!
&rlm;لابد أن هذا هو... &rlm;السيد "تاكيغوتشي"!
Shirakabe Hotel delivery, sir. I've brought the food you ordered.
&rlm;خدمة فندق "شيراكابي" لتوصيل الطعام &rlm;يا سيدي. أحضرت الطعام الذي طلبته.
He said he's from a hotel!
&rlm;يقول إنه من فندق.
No wonder it looks so delicious!
&rlm;لا عجب في ذلك، &rlm;الطعام يبدو شهياً للغاية!
Hey. Stare all you want, but you're not getting any.
&rlm;يمكنك أن تحملق كما تشاء، &rlm;لكن لن تحصل على أي منه.
Beat it.
&rlm;اغربوا عن وجهي!
There's no call to be so mean.
&rlm;ليس من الضروري أن تكون &rlm;شريراً إلى هذه الدرجة.
Thank you for coming. That was fast.
&rlm;شكراً لحضورك. وصلت بسرعة.
Nao Takiguchi (34) Company President's Wife
&rlm;"(ناو تاكيغوشي)، (43) &rlm;زوجة رئيس مجلس إدارة الشركة"
What a cute doggie!
&rlm;يا له من كلب لطيف!
His name is Koro. And that's such a pretty necklace!
&rlm;اسمه "كورو".
Thank you, but this is just a cheap acrylic piece.
&rlm;شكراً، لكنها قطعة رخيصة &rlm;من الأكريليك.
Ma'am, where would you like the food?
&rlm;يا سيدتي، &rlm;أين تريدينني أن أضع الطعام؟
Oh, I'm sorry. Could I trouble you to bring it aboard?
&rlm;آسفة، هل يمكنك أن تحضره &rlm;على متن اليخت؟
You children come, too.
&rlm;أيها الأطفال، تعالوا أنتم كذلك.
But...
&rlm;- لكن... &rlm;- أنت حتى لا تعرفيننا، لا يمكننا...
This hotel's food is delicious. You want some, don't you?
&rlm;طعام هذا الفندق شهي. &rlm;ترغبون في بعض منه، أليس كذلك؟
But if we eat, there won't be enough left for you.
&rlm;لكن لو أكلنا، &rlm;لن يتبقى ما يكفي من أجلك.
Kids shouldn't stand on formalities.
&rlm;لا يجب للأطفال أن يهتموا بالرسميات.
Kotarou Takiguchi (55) Company President
&rlm;"(كوتارو تاكيغوتشي)، (55) &rlm;رئيس مجلس إدارة الشركة"
We ordered more than we could eat and planned to have the leftovers tonight.
&rlm;لقد طلبنا كمية أكبر مما يمكننا أكله &rlm;وكنا ننوي تناول ما يتبقى منه الليلة.
We can really eat it, then?
&rlm;إذن يمكننا فعلاً أن نأكله؟
Yes. I was just thinking that it would be lonely to eat by ourselves.
&rlm;أجل، كنت أفكر للتو أننا &rlm;سنشعر بالوحدة لو أكلناه وحدنا.
You're more than welcome to join us.
&rlm;نرحب بكم كثيراً للانضمام إلينا.
In that case...
&rlm;في تلك الحالة...
We accept!
&rlm;سنقبل الدعوة!
A chic and dashing detective show that holds up under the blazing sun!
&rlm;حلقات بوليسية راقيه مثيرة &rlm;تتمتع بشعبية كبيرة.
We're all witnesses! A millionaire dives into the sea!
&rlm;جميعنا شهود! &rlm;مليونير يغطس في البحر!
Always determining the one truth with the body of a child and the mind of an adult,
&rlm;دائماً يعثر على الحقيقة &rlm;بجسد طفل وذهن رجل بالغ
His name is Detective Conan!
&rlm;اسمه المحقق "كونان"!
The Man Who Was Betrayed by the Sea
&rlm;الرجل الذي خانه البحر
Where the heck did those three go?
&rlm;أين ذهب أولئك الثلاثة &rlm;بحق السماء؟
It's your own fault for coming to the beach and doing nothing but sleep.
&rlm;إنه ذنبك لمجيئك إلى الشاطىء &rlm;وعدم قيامك بأي شيء فيما عدا النوم.
If we don't find them soon,
&rlm;إذا لم نعثر عليهم عما قريب،
we're gonna eat those bentos without them.
&rlm;فسنأكل ذلك الغداء &rlm;المعد مسبقاً وحدنا.
If we do that, they'll never forgive us.
&rlm;لو فعلنا ذلك، فلن يغفروه لنا أبداً.
Hell hath no fury like a stomach scorned.
&rlm;لا شيء أسوأ من غضب &rlm;معدة جائعة.
Good point.
&rlm;معك حق.
Conan and Haibara are gonna be so sorry
&rlm;"كونان" و"هايبارا" سيندمان كثيراً
that they missed out on such delicious food!
&rlm;لأنهما فاتهما مثل هذا الطعام الشهي!
Don't worry about them!
&rlm;لا تقلق عليهما!
It's his own fault for sleeping after coming all the way to the beach!
&rlm;إنه ذنبه لأنه نام &rlm;بعدما جاء كل هذه المسافة إلى الشاطىء!
More friends of yours are here?
&rlm;أهناك المزيد من أصدقائكم هنا؟
We're really good friends!
&rlm;نحن أصدقاء مقربون!
But Haibara said that she didn't want to get a sunburn!
&rlm;لكن "هايبارا" قالت إنها &rlm;لا تريد أن تصاب بحرق من الشمس!
Oh?
&rlm;حقاً؟
If a grade-schooler is worried about her skin,
&rlm;لو كانت فتاة في المرحلة الابتدائية &rlm;تقلق على بشرتها،
I can't wait to see what sort of beauty she grows into.
&rlm;لا أطيق الانتظار حتى أرى &rlm;كم ستكون جميلة عندما تكبر.
Conan is in grade school, but spends all his time reading mystery novels.
&rlm;"كونان" في المرحلة الابتدائية، لكنه يقضي &rlm;كل وقته في قراءة الروايات البوليسية.
He doesn't really act like a kid!
&rlm;في الواقع لا يتصرف كطفل!
He's such a nerd.
&rlm;إنه مهووس تماماً بها.
Gosh, I'm ever so sorry for being a nerd.
&rlm;أنا آسف للغاية لأنني مهووس.
Conan!
&rlm;"كونان"!
Then this cutie is Miss Haibara?
&rlm;إذن هذه اللطيفة هي الآنسة "هايبارا"؟
Yes. You'll have to excuse me for not being a full-grown beauty yet, though.
&rlm;أجل، لكن لابد أن تعذرني لأنني لست &rlm;فتاة ناضجة جميلة بعد.
You're plenty beautiful already. For a grade-schooler, of course.
&rlm;أنت جميلة كثيراً بالفعل. بالنسبة &rlm;لفتاة في المرحلة الابتدائية بالتأكيد.
What are you guys doing here?
&rlm;ماذا تفعلون هنا؟
We could ask the same thing.
&rlm;يمكننا أن نسأل نفس السؤال.
We were out looking for you so we could finally eat our bento lunches.
&rlm;كنا نبحث عنكم كي يمكننا &rlm;أخيراً أن نأكل غداءنا المعد مسبقاً.
I don't mean to disparage what your mothers made for you,
&rlm;لا أقصد أن أقلل من شأن &rlm;ما أعدته أمهاتكم من أجلكم،
but surely you can eat them on the way home, can't you?
&rlm;لكن مؤكد يمكنكم تناوله وأنتم في &rlm;طريق العودة إلى منازلكم، أليس كذلك؟ &rlm;أرجو أن تنضموا إلينا لتناول الغداء.
Yeah, do it! This roast beef is great!
&rlm;أجل، قوما بذلك، اللحم البقري &rlm;المطهو في الفرن ممتاز!
This spiny lobster is the best!
&rlm;وهذا الجراد للبحر هو الأفضل!
Yeah!
&rlm;أجل!
Mitsuhiko! Don't hog that lobster!
&rlm;"ميتسوهيكو"، لا تلتهم ذلك الكركند!
This is a spiny lobster!
&rlm;إنه جراد بحر!
That's not the same thing?
&rlm;هذا ليس نفس الشيء؟
Darling.
&rlm;يا عزيزي.
The children will laugh at you.
&rlm;سيضحك الأطفال عليك.
You're like a couple of newlyweds!
&rlm;إنكما مثل ثنائي حديث الزواج!
Well, we just got married six months ago.
&rlm;لقد تزوجنا منذ ستة أشهر فقط.
And this is my first marriage.
&rlm;وهذا هو زواجي الأول.
I spent so much time on my company
&rlm;قضيت وقتاً طويلاً في بناء شركتي
that I forgot to get married until late in life.
&rlm;لدرجة أنني نسيت أن أتزوج &rlm;حتى وقت متأخر في حياتي.
I'm jealous!
&rlm;أشعر بالغيرة!
It'd be so great to go out to sea on a ship like this and swim in the ocean!
&rlm;يكون رائعاً أن أبحر في المحيط &rlm;في مركب كهذا وأسبح في مياهه!
Forget about it! You're not a very good swimmer yet, remember?
&rlm;تناسي الأمر! لستي سباحة ماهرة بعد، &rlm;تذكري ذلك؟
If I lived on a ship like this, I'd learn to swim in no time!
&rlm;لو كنت أعيش على مركب كهذا، &rlm;لتعلمت السباحة في وقت قصير!
That's the spirit, Ayumi! Never let things get you down!
&rlm;هذه هي الروح المطلوبة يا "أيومي"! &rlm;لا تترك أي شيء يحبط عزيمتك!
I couldn't swim either, and I'm 53! But I practiced hard, and now I can!
&rlm;لم أكن أجيد السباحة أنا أيضاً وعمري 35 &rlm;عاماً لكنني تدربت كثيراً، والآن يمكنني ذلك!
People can do anything if they set their minds to it!
&rlm;يمكن للناس أن تقوم بأي شيء &rlm;إذا صمموا عليه!
You joined a health club, didn't you?
&rlm;التحقت بناد رياضي، &rlm;أليس كذلك؟
No, we just had a new house built, so we had a pool put in.
&rlm;كلا، قمنا ببناء منزل جديد، &rlm;لذا بنينا فيه مسبحاً.
Let me show you something amazing!
&rlm;دعني أريكم شيئاً مذهلاً!
You made a video of that?
&rlm;صورت فيديو لذلك؟
Cut it out, it's embarrassing!
&rlm;كفي عن هذا، إنه أمر محرج!
But by the end, look!
&rlm;لكن في النهاية، انظروا!
You're right!
&rlm;أنت محق!
You're really swimming!
&rlm;أنت تسبح فعلاً!
Sweet! Then let's race to see who can reach that embankment first!
&rlm;لطيف! إذن دعنا نتسابق لنرى &rlm;من يمكنه أن يصل للجسر أولاً!
You can use a swim ring, Ayumi!
&rlm;يمكنك أن تستخدم طوف نجاة يا "أيومي"!
-Okay, you're on! -No!
&rlm;- حسناً، اتفقنا! &rlm;- كلا!
You just drank some wine.
&rlm;لقد تناولت للتو بعض النبيذ.
And your blood pressure is high as it is. You should rest first.
&rlm;وضغط الدم لديك مرتفع من الأصل. &rlm;يجب أن تستريح أولاً.
Dang, I was sure that I had it in the bag!
&rlm;تبا!ً كنت واثقاً من الفوز!
How old is Koro?
&rlm;كم يبلغ عمر "كورو"؟
He just turned 1.
&rlm;لقد أكمل عامه الأول للتو.
Hm? The buckle on his collar is rusted.
&rlm;إبزيم طوقه صدأ.
Oh, maybe that's because we go for walkies even when it's raining.
&rlm;ربما لأننا نذهب للتنزه &rlm;حتى لو كان الجو ممطراً.
Hey, we should head back.
&rlm;يجب أن نعود.
Oops, I forgot.
&rlm;لقد نسيت.
Running off and stuffing your faces without telling me...
&rlm;أن تهربوا وتلتهموا كل ذلك &rlm;الطعام بدون أن تخبروني...
Someone should have come back and told me.
&rlm;كان يجب أن يعود أحدكم &rlm;ليخبرني.
I was so worried that I was this close to calling the police.
&rlm;قلقت للغاية لدرجة أنني أوشكت &rlm;أن أتصل بالشرطة.
It's bad for your digestion if you eat while angry.
&rlm;الأكل عند الغضب يضر بالهضم.
Yahoo!
&rlm;متوحش!
Here it comes!
&rlm;ها هي تأتي!
Nice shot!
&rlm;رمية جيدة!
Catch!
&rlm;امسك هذه!
Huh?
&rlm;ماذا؟
Isn't that the Takiguchis' ship that's heading out?
&rlm;أليس هذا يخت "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;الذي يتجه نحو المياه العميقة؟
You're right!
&rlm;أنت محق!
Yeah! Nao just came out on deck, too!
&rlm;أجل! "ناو" كذلك خرجت للتو &rlm;إلى سطح اليخت!
Is he planning to do some swimming?
&rlm;هل ينوي أن يسبح؟
Hey, Pops! Thanks for the grub earlier!
&rlm;شكراً يا صديقي على الطعام &rlm;الذي قدمته لنا مسبقاً!
Let's swim, too!
&rlm;لنسبح نحن كذلك!
Good idea!
&rlm;فكرة جيدة!
-I'll go get my swim ring! -What's going on?! This isn't right!
&rlm;- سأذهب لأحضر طوف النجاة! &rlm;- ما الذي يحدث؟ هذا لا يبدو أمرا مطمئناً!
S-Somebody! Somebody, help!
&rlm;النجدة! ساعدوني!
Oh, no! He's drowning!
&rlm;كلا، إنه يغرق!
Darling!
&rlm;يا عزيزي!
Tokyo Fire Department
&rlm;"إدارة (طوكيو) للحريق"
I'm really worried...
&rlm;أنا قلق حقاً...
I don't really feel like playing anymore, you know?
&rlm;لم أعد أرغب في اللعب
Yeah...
&rlm;أجل...
There's plenty of daylight left, but I think we should head home.
&rlm;ما زال هناك كثير من ضوء النهار &rlm;لكن أعتقد يجب أن نعود للمنزل.
We can call the fire department later to check in on Mr. Takiguchi.
&rlm;يمكننا أن نتصل بإدارة الحريق في وقت لاحق &rlm;لنطمئن على السيد "تاكيغوتشي".
You're the children who were with the Takiguchis earlier, aren't you?
&rlm;أنتم الأطفال الذين كنتم مع &rlm;آل "تاكيغوتشي" في وقت مبكر، أليس كذلك؟
When I got to their boat to pick up our dishes, no one was there.
&rlm;عندما ذهبت إلى يختهم لأستعيد الأطباق &rlm;لم يكن هناك أحد.
Do you know what's going on?
&rlm;هل تعرفون ما الخطب؟
Oh, we'll get your dishes for you, then.
&rlm;سنحضر لك أطباقك.
Oh, right... They didn't let you ride in the ambulance, did they?
&rlm;أجل... لم يسمحوا لكم بالذهاب &rlm;في سيارة الإسعاف، أليس كذلك؟
We should bring them their clothes, shouldn't we?
&rlm;يجب أن نحضر لهما ملابسهما، &rlm;أليس كذلك؟
Oh, I guess we should.
&rlm;أظن يجب أن نفعل ذلك.
You're certain it was an accident?
&rlm;أنت متأكد أنه كان حادثاً؟
Emergency Care Center
&rlm;- "مركز رعاية الطوارىء" &rlm;- لقد بدأنا التحقيقات للتو،
but from eyewitness accounts, it seems clear that he dove in voluntarily.
&rlm;لكن من أقوال الشهود، &rlm;يبدو من الواضح أنه غطس بمحض إرادته.
Ryouichi Katagiri (48) Takiguchi's Assistant
&rlm;"(رايتشوي كاتاغيري)، (84) &rlm;مساعد (تاكيغوتشي)"
I can't believe that. Isn't it possible that someone pushed him in?
&rlm;لا يمكنني أن أصدق ذلك، &rlm;أليس من المحتمل أن أحدهم قد دفعه؟
He and his wife were the only two people on the ship.
&rlm;هو وزوجته كانا الوحيدين على متن المركب.
Det. Nagai (38)
&rlm;"المحقق (ناغاي)، (83)"
Are you implying that she shoved him in?
&rlm;هل تلمح أنها دفعته نحو الماء؟
Of course not, but Mr. Takiguchi told me a story once.
&rlm;كلا، بالتأكيد، لكن السيد "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;حكى لي قصة في إحدى المرات.
He almost drowned in a river as a child,
&rlm;كاد يغرق في نهر وهو طفل،
and has been too afraid of the water ever since to learn to swim!
&rlm;وظل يخشى الماء من ذلك الحين &rlm;بحيث لم يتعلم السباحة!
He practiced really hard recently and learned how.
&rlm;لقد تدرب كثيراً مؤخراً وتعلم السباحة.
Who are you?
&rlm;من أنت؟
Oh, pardon the interruption.
&rlm;المعذرة على مقاطعتي لكم.
These children made friends with the Takiguchis at the beach.
&rlm;هؤلاء الأطفال تعرفوا على آل "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;عند الشاطىء.
They were very kind to the children, so they wanted to come see how he's doing.
&rlm;كانا لطيفين جداً مع الأطفال &rlm;لذا أرادوا الحضور والاطمئنان عليه.
We brought them their clothes!
&rlm;أحضرنا لهما ملابسهما!
And Koro was left behind.
&rlm;وقد تركا "كورو" وحده.
What's Mr. Takiguchi's condition?
&rlm;كيف حال السيد "تاكيغوتشي"؟
I'm not sure how to break this to you,
&rlm;لا أعرف كيف أقول لكم هذا،
but he was pronounced dead a few minutes ago.
&rlm;لكن تم إعلان وفاته منذ بضع دقائق.
But that's... How could someone so nice die?
&rlm;لكن هذا... كيف يمكن &rlm;لشخص لطيف مثله أن يموت؟
I can't believe it...
&rlm;لا يمكنني أن أصدق ذلك...
Anyway, Detective, please find out for sure if this really was an accident!
&rlm;على أية حال أيها المحقق، أرجوك &rlm;أن تتأكد إذا كان ذلك فعلاً حادثاً!
I warned him again and again before they got married
&rlm;حذرته مرة بعد أخرى عندما تزوجا
that she was only after his money!
&rlm;إنها فقط تسعى للحصول على أمواله!
He was completely taken in by that woman,
&rlm;لكنه فتن تماماً بتلك المرأة،
and now look what's happened!
&rlm;والآن انظروا ماذا حدث!
Are you saying that Nao did this?!
&rlm;هل تقول إن "ناو" فعلت ذلك؟
A nice lady like her could never do something bad!
&rlm;سيدة لطيفة مثلها لا يمكن أبداً &rlm;أن تقوم بشيء سيىء كهذا!
Now, now...
&rlm;اهدأ...
You'll have to forgive them. Are you with Mr. Takiguchi's company?
&rlm;لابد أن تسامحهم هل تعمل &rlm;في شركة السيد "تاكيغوتشي"؟
Yes, I'm Katagiri, his executive assistant.
&rlm;أجل، أنا "كاتاغيري" &rlm;مساعده التنفيذي.
Did you see the accident?
&rlm;هل رأيتم الحادث؟
We sure did!
&rlm;بالتأكيد رأيناه!
Mr. Takiguchi drowned right in front of us!
&rlm;السيد "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;غرق أمامنا مباشرةً!
He waved to us and then dove into the water!
&rlm;لقد لوح لنا ثم غطس أمامنا!
I see... I know it's a lot, but can you come down to the station
&rlm;فهمت... أعرف أنه طلب كبير، &rlm;لكن هل يمكنكم أن تأتوا إلى المخفر
and tell me exactly what you saw?
&rlm;وتخبرونني بالضبط ماذا رأيتم؟
-Sure! -Yes, sir.
&rlm;- بالتأكيد! &rlm;- أجل، يا سيدي.
When Mr. Takiguchi dove in,
&rlm;عندما غطس السيد &rlm;"تاكيغوتشي" في الماء،
do you know where Mrs. Takiguchi was?
&rlm;أتعرفون أين كانت السيدة "تاكيغوتشي"؟
She was standing a little bit away, doing something.
&rlm;كانت تقف بعيداً بعض الشيء &rlm;تقوم بشيء ما.
I think she might have been cleaning up the lunch dishes.
&rlm;أعتقد ربما كانت تنظف أطباق الغداء.
I see. Maybe that explains why she was slow to notice him drowning.
&rlm;فهمت، ربما ذلك يفسر لماذا &rlm;تأخرت في ملاحظة أنه يغرق.
Come in.
&rlm;تفضل بالدخول.
Nao!
&rlm;"ناو"!
Ayumi... Thank you for bringing my clothes.
&rlm;"أيومي"... &rlm;شكراً لإحضارك ملابسي.
Nao? Where's your necklace?
&rlm;"ناو"؟ أين قلادتك؟
I guess the chain broke
&rlm;أظن أن السلسلة كسرت
when I was trying to save my husband and it sank to the bottom.
&rlm;عندما كنت أحاول إنقاذ زوجي &rlm;وسقطت في القاع.
I've gotten statements from these children,
&rlm;لقد حصلت على إفادات هؤلاء الأطفال،
and it seems clear that your husband dove into the water voluntarily.
&rlm;ويبدو من الواضح أن زوجك &rlm;غطس في الماء بمحض إرادته.
I think it's safe to write this off as an unfortunate accident.
&rlm;أعتقد يمكن أن نعتبر هذا حادثاً مؤسفاً.
It was all my fault.
&rlm;كان كل ذلك ذنبي.
Even if he said he could swim just fine,
&rlm;حتى لو قال إنه يمكنه السباحة جيداً،
if I'd been paying closer attention, maybe he...
&rlm;لو كنت أراقبه بحرص، ربما كان...
The last question I had for you has to do with that.
&rlm;آخر سؤال لدي من أجلك يتعلق بذلك؟
An employee at the company said that Mr. Takiguchi told him he couldn't swim.
&rlm;موظف في الشركة قال إن السيد &rlm;"تاكيغوتشي" قال له إنه لا يجيد السباحة.
Had he really learned how? You should show it to him! You know, that video of him practicing!
&rlm;هل تعلم السباحة حقاً؟
Oh, right.
&rlm;أجل.
This was recorded during his first lesson in the pool at home.
&rlm;صور هذا خلال أول درس له &rlm;في المسبح بالمنزل.
I had our housekeeper film it.
&rlm;جعلت مدبرة المنزل تصوره له.
You're doing it!
&rlm;أنت تسبح بالفعل!
And this one was recorded last week.
&rlm;وهذا تم تصويره في الأسبوع الماضي.
That's the way! Keep it up! Now turn without stopping!
&rlm;هذه هي الطريقة! استمر في ذلك! &rlm;الآن در بدون أن تتوقف!
I see... He had definitely learned how to swim.
&rlm;فهمت... كان بالتأكيد قد تعلم السباحة.
Come with me for a minute.
&rlm;تعال معي لدقيقة.
What is it, Conan?
&rlm;ما الخطب يا "كونان"؟
Can I see your video camera?
&rlm;أيمكنني أن أرى كاميرا الفيديو &rlm;الخاصة بك؟
Sure, I guess.
&rlm;بالتأكيد، تفضل.
Is something important recorded on there?
&rlm;أهناك شيء مهم مسجل هنا؟
You're right!
&rlm;أنت محق!
Yeah! Nao just came out on deck, too!
&rlm;أجل، "ناو" خرجت إلى سطح &rlm;المركب للتو، كذلك!
Good, there's audio, too.
&rlm;جيد، التسجيل بالصوت كذلك.
The important part is coming up.
&rlm;الجزء المهم هو التالي.
Let's swim, too!
&rlm;لنسبح نحن أيضاً.
Good idea!
&rlm;فكرة جيدة!
-I'll go get my swim ring! -What's going on?! This isn't right!
&rlm;- سأذهب لأحضر طوف النجاة! &rlm;- ما الذي يحدث؟ يبدو أن هناك مشكلة!
S-Somebody! Somebody, help!
&rlm;النجدة! ساعدوني!
This is it.
&rlm;هذا هو الجزء.
This can zoom in, right?
&rlm;هذه الكاميرا يمكنها أن تقترب &rlm;أكثر وتكبر اللقطة، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah, the image will be degraded, though.
&rlm;أجل، لكن الصورة سيقل وضوحها.
S-Somebody! Somebody, help!
&rlm;النجدة، ساعدوني!
Darling!
&rlm;يا عزيزي!
What's going on?
&rlm;ما الخطب؟
There's a pause between when Nao notices that Kotarou is drowning
&rlm;هناك فترة توقف بين ملاحظة "ناو" &rlm;أن "كوتارو" يغرق
and when she dives in to help him.
&rlm;وعندما تغطس لمساعدته.
And their cabin cruiser had a life preserver.
&rlm;والمركب البخاري كان به طوف نجاة.
Why didn't she use it?
&rlm;لماذا لم تستخدمه؟
And what about that thing I noticed in those swim practice videos?
&rlm;وماذا عن الشيء الذي لاحظته &rlm;في فيديوهات التدريب على السباحة؟
Was Kotarou really...
&rlm;هل كان "كوتارو" فعلا.ً..
What are you two whispering about out here?
&rlm;ما الذي تتهامسان فيه هناك بالخارج؟
Oh, um...
&rlm;إنه...
Hm? The buckle on his collar is rusted.
&rlm;الإبزيم في طوقه صدأ.
Oh, maybe that's because we go for walkies even when it's raining.
&rlm;ربما ذلك لأننا نذهب للتنزه &rlm;حتى لو كان الجو ممطراً.
That's it!
&rlm;لقد وجدتها!
I'm sorry to have put you to all this trouble, everyone, but you can go now.
&rlm;آسف لأنني أخذت من وقتكم جميعاً، &rlm;لكن يمكنكم الرحيل الآن.
I'll take you back to the hospital, Ma'am.
&rlm;سآخذك مرة أخرى للمستشفى يا سيدتي.
Thank you for your assistance.
&rlm;شكراً على مساعدتكم.
Could I trouble you to put that off for a bit?
&rlm;هل يمكنك أن تؤجل هذا قليلاً؟
Is there a something that you would like to add?
&rlm;هل ترغب في إضافة شيء ما؟
Oh, no, um...
&rlm;كلا...
This was no accident. It was premeditated murder.
&rlm;هذه لم تكن حادثة، &rlm;كانت جريمة قتل عن عمد.
It was what?!
&rlm;كانت ماذا؟
But Mr. Takiguchi dove into the water himself!
&rlm;لكن السيد "تاكيغوتشي" غطس &rlm;في الماء بنفسه!
Yes, but if he'd known that he couldn't swim,
&rlm;أجل، لكن لو كان يعرف &rlm;أنه لا يجيد السباحة،
he wouldn't have dove in, would he?
&rlm;ما كان قد غطس، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Takiguchi was made to believe that he could swim
&rlm;لقد تم إقناع السيد "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;أنه يجيد السباحة
and then brought out in their cabin cruiser to water too deep to stand in.
&rlm;ثم أخرج في مركبه البخاري &rlm;إلى مياه عميقة لا يمكن الوقوف فيها.
Wouldn't you call that murder?
&rlm;ألا تسمي هذا قتلاً؟
Isn't that right, Nao Takiguchi?
&rlm;أليس هذا صحيحاً يا "ناو تاكيغوتشي"؟
My husband was fully capable of swimming.
&rlm;كان زوجي يجيد السباحة تماماً
You saw it with your own two eyes.
&rlm;لقد رأيت ذلك بعينيك.
Or has that video been doctored in some way?
&rlm;أم أن هذا الفيديو تم تزويره بشكل ما؟
No, that video was genuine. Mr. Takiguchi could swim.
&rlm;كلا، ذلك الفيديو كان حقيقياً. &rlm;السيد "تاكيغوتشي" كان يجيد السباحة.
What are you trying to say?
&rlm;ما الذي تحاول أن تقوله؟
He could swim,
&rlm;كان يمكنه السباحة،
but only in his own pool.
&rlm;لكن فقط في مسبحه.
-Conan? -Coming!
&rlm;- "كونان" &rlm;- إنني قادم!
Can I borrow this?
&rlm;هل يمكنني أن أقترض هذا؟
Look at Nao's necklace in the video where he was practicing his kicks.
&rlm;انظر إلى قلادة "ناو" في الفيديو &rlm;عندما كان يتدرب على ركلاته.
See? It's hanging down in the water.
&rlm;انظر، إنها متدلية إلى أسفل في الماء.
But on the last day...
&rlm;لكن في اليوم الأخير...
See? Now it's floating.
&rlm;رأيت؟ إنها تطفو الآن.
L-Let me see that!
&rlm;دعني أرى ذلك!
I-It's hanging down in one and floating in the other, all right!
&rlm;إنها متدلية في فيديو، &rlm;وتطفو في آخر، فعلاً!
Can you explain this in layman's terms?
&rlm;هل يمكنك أن تشرح ذلك &rlm;بكلمات مبسطة.
It was Koro who told me why it is that her necklace is floating.
&rlm;"كورو" &rlm;هو الذي فسر لي سبب طفو قلادتها.
The buckle of Koro's collar, which should only be one year old,
&rlm;إبزيم طوق "كورو"، &rlm;المفروض أن يكون عمره عاماً واحداً،
is covered in rust for some reason.
&rlm;لكن يغطيه الصدأ لسبب ما.
You poured a huge amount of bath salts into the pool, Mrs. Takiguchi.
&rlm;لقد سكبت كمية هائلة من أملاح الاستحمام &rlm;في المسبح يا سيدة "تاكيغوتشي".
To make his body more buoyant.
&rlm;كي تجعلي جسمه يطفو بشكل أسهل.
The necklace in the video is acrylic.
&rlm;القلادة في الفيديو من الأكريليك.
The specific gravity of acrylic ranges from 1.17 to 1.2,
&rlm;الجاذبية النوعية للأكريليك تتراوح &rlm;ما بين 1،17 إلى 2،1
so the specific gravity of the pool water last week was greater than that.
&rlm;لذا الجاذبية النوعية بماء المسبح &rlm;كانت أكثر من ذلك.
Isn't that right, Mrs. Takiguchi?
&rlm;أليس هذا صحيحاً يا سيدة "تاكيغوتشي"؟
You're wrong, If I had put in that much bath salt,
&rlm;أنت مخطىء، لو كنت وضعت &rlm;في المسبح كل هذا الملح للاستحمام
even a dimwit like my husband would have noticed.
&rlm;حتى شخص مغفل مثل زوجي &rlm;كان سيلاحظ ذلك.
What did you put in there, then?
&rlm;ماذا وضعت إذن بالمسبح؟
The necklace that sank into the sea is floating in that video.
&rlm;القلادة التي غرقت في البحر &rlm;تطفو في ذلك الفيديو.
In any event, we've established that the pool water in the video
&rlm;على أية حال، &rlm;لقد أثبتنا أن مياه المسبح في الفيديو
has a high specific gravity.
&rlm;لها جاذبية نوعية عالية.
Shall we go to your house and examine it?
&rlm;هل نذهب إلى منزلك ونفحصها؟
Feel free, but there isn't any water. I drained the pool.
&rlm;يمكنك الذهاب إلى هناك، &rlm;لكنني أفرغت المسبح من المياه.
I wouldn't underestimate the police.
&rlm;لا تقللي من قدرات الشرطة.
If there is anything at all left in the pool,
&rlm;لو تبقى أي شيء بالمرة &rlm;في المسبح،
they'll quickly find out exactly what was dissolved in the water.
&rlm;فسيكتشفون بسرعة بالضبط &rlm;ما الذي تم إذابته في المياه.
Ma'am, is what this man saying true?
&rlm;سيدتي، هل ما يقوله هذا الرجل صحيح؟
Answer me!
&rlm;أجيبيني!
Nao! It's not true, is it?!
&rlm;"ناو" هذا ليس صحيحاً، أليس كذلك؟
It's true.
&rlm;إنه صحيح.
As this man said, I poured in bath salt at first,
&rlm;كما قال هذا الرجل، &rlm;سكبت ملح استحمام أولاً،
but when I increased the amount, my husband noticed.
&rlm;لكن عندما أضفت كمية زائدة &rlm;لاحظ زوجي ذلك.
After that, I switched to a water-soluble polymer.
&rlm;بعد ذلك استبدلته ببوليمير يذوب بالماء.
A harmless kind used in medicines and food.
&rlm;نوع غير مضر يستخدم &rlm;في الأدوية والطعام.
The specific gravity of the water last week must have gone above 1.3.
&rlm;الجاذبية النوعية للماء الأسبوع &rlm;الماضي لابد أن تكون قد زادت عن 1،3.
1.3 is the same as that of the Dead Sea,
&rlm;1،3 هي نفس الجاذبية النوعية للبحر الميت.
where you're supposedly able to read a book while floating.
&rlm;حيث يقولون إنك يمكنك &rlm;أن تقرأ كتاباً وأنت تطفو في الماء.
It's no surprise that Mr. Takiguchi mistakenly believed that he could swim.
&rlm;فلا عجب أن السيد "تاكيغوتشي" &rlm;أعتقد عن طريق الخطأ أنه يجيد السباحة.
You probably made that video for when you were questioned by the police,
&rlm;غالباً قمت بتسجيل هذا الفيديو &rlm;في حالة استجواب الشرطة لك
but the footage in it backfired on you.
&rlm;لكنه بعض ما سجل فيه تحول &rlm;إلى دليل ضدك.
The only thing he ever thought of was expanding his company.
&rlm;الشيء الوحيد الذي كان يفكر &rlm;فيه هو التوسع في شركته.
He would use any dirty tactic without a second thought.
&rlm;كان يستخدم أي أسلوب رخيص &rlm;بدون تردد.
Without caring how many people he made suffer as a result.
&rlm;بدون أن يهتم بعدد &rlm;من سيعانون نتيجة لذلك.
So I planned to make him suffer this time.
&rlm;لذا خططت لأن يعاني هذه المرة.
Being with that man with no common sense or education was a living hell.
&rlm;حياتي مع ذلك الرجل الذي لم يمتلك أي تعقل &rlm;أو تعليم كان جحيماً.
I couldn't take it anymore.
&rlm;لم أستطع تحمل المزيد.
Mr. Takiguchi was obsessed with making money, all right,
&rlm;السيد "تاكيغوتشي" كان مهووساً &rlm;بجني المال بالتأكيد
and perhaps he was lacking in common sense and education,
&rlm;وربما كان ينقصه التعقل والتعليم،
but wouldn't you say that he had far more humanity in him than you,
&rlm;لكن ألا تعتقدين أنه كان لديه كم &rlm;من الإنسانية أكثر كثيراً منك،
a woman who would commit murder to get her revenge?
&rlm;فأنت امرأة ترتكب جريمة قتل &rlm;لتحقق انتقامها؟
I trusted her because she was so nice.
&rlm;لقد وثقت بها لأنها كانت لطيفة جداً.
When she invited us to eat with them, I thought she was a good person.
&rlm;عندما دعتني لتناول الطعام معهما &rlm;ظننت أنها شخص طيب.
I'm never trusting adults again!
&rlm;لن أثق في البالغين أبداً بعد اليوم.
There are all sorts of adults. All shapes and sizes.
&rlm;هناك أنواع كثيرة من البالغين. &rlm;من جميع الأشكال والأحجام.
That's true.
&rlm;هذا صحيح.
I myself still have a pure heart after all these years!
&rlm;أنا عن نفسي ما زلت أحتفظ &rlm;بقلب نقي بعد كل هذه السنين!
Was that laugh because of how purehearted I am?
&rlm;هل هذا الضحك لأنني نقي القلب؟
Hey, don't we still have those bento boxes left?
&rlm;أما زالت لدينا علب الغداء؟
Oh, right! We were treated to lunch, so we still have our bento boxes!
&rlm;أجل، لقد تمت دعوتنا للغداء، &rlm;لذا ما زالت علب غدائنا موجودة.
Let's go eat 'em!
&rlm;لنذهب لنأكلها!
Now that you mention it, I'm starving!
&rlm;الآن بما أنك ذكرت ذلك &rlm;أتضور جوعاً!
I wonder what's in them!
&rlm;ترى ماذا يوجد بداخلها!